## Q ABOUT ME

I'm a passionate User Experience Designer with knowledge in the user-centered design. I advocate for user needs through planning, design and implementation ensuring all output reflects a solid understanding of UX principles.

I have a strong desire to inspire creativity, innovative thinking and offer compelling solutions that translate into building world-class interactive experiences and products across all digital platforms. Working closely with engineering, research and business lines, I have contributed to the development of interface design, interaction models, content structure, ensuring that all of them reflect a clear understanding of target audience behavior, meet their expectations and user needs.

## 2 CONTACT ME

- geunbae-lee.com
- in linkedin.com/in/geunbaelee
- dribbble.com/geunbae-lee
- gblee@gatech.edu
- (404)909-6013
- Atlanta, GA

## X MY SKILLS

- UX Design / Interaction Design / HCI
- UX Research (SPSS / Survey / User Testing)
- Microsoft Word / Excel / Powerpoint
- Sketch / Photoshop / Illustrator
- HTML5 / CSS3 / Javascript / jQuery
- Framer.js / Invision / Origami / Prototpie
- Balsamiq Mockups / Axure RP
- Java / Python / C# / Arduino
- AR / VR (Unity / Vuforia)
- Intuitive / Problem Solver / Collaborative Creative / Communicative / Visionary Passionate / Detail oriented

# Geunbae Lee

#### **Incoming Product Design Intern at Facebook**

Portfolio Website: http://geunbae-lee.com



## **EDUCATION**



Master of Science in Human Computer Interaction



Bachelor of Arts in Psychology with 2 years in Mechanical Engineering

Lambda University of Michigan - Ann Arbor Sep 2009 - May 2015



## EXPERIENCE

#### Product Design Intern

Facebook May 2017 - Aug 2017

#### Graduate Research Assistant

- Georgia Tech Research Network and Operations Center Dec 2016 Present
- Continuing with the self-initiated project (GT Find Class) as a UX Designer and a front-end developer. GT Find Class is an application that assists students to find classes based on their class schedule.
- Designing a mobile app for a Smart Grill monitor which will also be launched as a half-day IoT curriculum for the Georgia Tech Professional Education.
- Producing visual designs including posters, banners, logos for apps, and other kinds of UI elements.

#### Graduate Assistant

- Initiated a project (HTML5 application) to help Georgia Tech students find classrooms based on their schedule.
- Managed GT-RNOC Lab website CIC and GT Journey website using Drupal.
- Worked closely with 3 developers and a professor as a UX Designer on an IoT project which aims to alleviate Atlanta's traffic problem.
- Produced visual designs including posters, logos for apps, and UI elements for various apps.

#### UI/UX Design Intern

HeyKorean Inc Ct 2015 - Jun 2016

- Designed K-TOWN app's restaurant coupon UI/UX which allows the users to use coupons to get discounts. It brought over 10% increase in the daily app usage.
- Created wireframes, prototypes and lo-fi designs for HeyKorean Customer Service Center renovation project which ultimately brought 6% increase in usage.
- Produced visual, interaction designs as well as designs and prototypes for the company's website and apps using Sketch, Photoshop, Axure and Framer.js

## PROJECTS

#### Designing Cancer Care for Kids (DuckTab)

• An app designed for Children's Healthcare of Atlanta (CHOA) to help bring positive user experience to the children and the parents during their clinic journey.

#### Whole New Grocery Shopping Experience (Grocery HelpAR)

• An app designed for international students which offers item translation, wayfinding, optional AR feature that allows item scanning for information to enhance their shopping experience.

#### Make Sure They Take Their Medication (MedMinder)

• There are three parts to this project: an app for caregivers to monitor the patients' medication, a ring that the patients wear to remind them when to take their medication and an interactive medication dispenser which communicates with the app and the ring.

# RECOGNITIONS

#### Net Impact Design Fellowship

• Representing Georgia Tech as a fellow to initiate an action project to enhance the campus community life for the students. Net Impact has selected only 10 students across the U.S.

#### IxDA Georgia Tech - Vice President

Running designing, prototyping workshops and events related to UI/UX/IxD/HCI.